<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Blois : Learn to Listen</string>
    <string name="action_settings">People interacting with the project Blois : Savoir Écouter</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="addUserPhoto">Add New User Image</string>
    <string name="addPhoto">Add Photo !</string>
    <string name="takePhoto">Take photo from camera</string>
    <string name="choosePhotoGallery">Choose from gallery</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="about_you">About you…</string>
    <string name="user_image">User Image</string>
    <string name="namelabel">label name edit box</string>
    <string name="aboutlabel">label about you edit box</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="title_activity_about">about project</string>

    <string name="aboutParagraph2">Blois : Savoir Écouter est un projet hybride. La structure de bois et papier est réelle, la tablette tactile est intégrée et les applications mobiles fournies sont numériques. Dans cette œuvre participative, les Blésois peuvent ajouter au contenu du projet soit un dessin, soit une histoire écrite à la main, soit des contenus numériques (sons, images ou vidéos).</string>
    <string name="about1Description">People interacting with the project Blois : Savoir Écouter</string>
    <string name="about2Description">detailed view of the sculpture Blois : Savoir Écouter</string>
    <string name="linkProject" translatable="false"><a href="http://http://blois.odeurdelacouleur.info">http://blois.odeurdelacouleur.info</a></string>
    <string name="title_activity_thanks">Our Thanks</string>
    <string name="title_activity_artist">About the Artist</string>
    <string name="title_activity_people">People of Blois</string>
    <string name="title_activity_legende">LegendeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_app">AppActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sound_list">SoundLIstActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sound">SoundActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sector_sounds">SectorSoundsActivity</string>


    <!--mystrings-->
    <string name="aboutDescription">About Project</string>
    <string name="thanksDescription">sound data</string>
    <string name="case1_Description" translatable="false">Sector 1</string>
    <string name="case2_Description" translatable="false">Sector 2</string>
    <string name="users_Description">people of Blois</string>
    <string name="case3_Description" translatable="false">Sector 3</string>
    <string name="case4_Description" translatable="false">Sector 4</string>
    <string name="case5_Description" translatable="false">Sector 5</string>
    <string name="case6_Description" translatable="false">Sector 6</string>
    <string name="case7_Description" translatable="false">Sector 7</string>
    <string name="case8_Description" translatable="false">Sector 8</string>
    <string name="case9_Description" translatable="false">Sector 9</string>
    <string name="case10_Description">Application Tour</string>
    <string name="case11_Description" translatable="false">Sector 11</string>
    <string name="case12_Description" translatable="false">Sector 12</string>
    <string name="case13_Description" translatable="false">Sector 13</string>
    <string name="case14_Description" translatable="false">Sector 14</string>
    <string name="case15_Description" translatable="false">Sector 15</string>
    <string name="legend_Description">The legend of map</string>
    <string name="application_Description">The application itself</string>
    <!--mystrings-->

    <string name="aboutParagraph1">Ce projet est né du désir de comprendre l’espace urbain dans un contexte sculptural. Mon objet est de créer un travail qui est un stimulant de l’engagement personnel avec l’espace urbain et des logiques socio-spatiales des individus et des communautés qu’ils composent. La démarche que j’ai adoptée pour réaliser l’oeuvre s’intègre dans une logique de long terme,
    dans la mesure où je souhaite cibler une grande variété de publics.</string>

    <string name="sound_image">Take photo from camera</string>
    <string name="aboutsoundlabel">Sound description</string>

    <string name="quadrantNum">This must change</string>
    <string name="number_of_sounds">- Practical information;</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_location_maps">Add Location</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_place">AddPlaceActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_zdetail_sound">Blois : Learn to Listen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_location">AddLocationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_people_detail">PeopleDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="sharing">Sharing</string>
    <string name="emailText">I would like to share this sound and I have read and understand the privacy policy of this application.</string>
    <string name="soundData">sound data</string>
    <string name="userData">User Data</string>
    <string name="locData">Location Data</string>
    <string name="search_hint">search…</string>
    <string name="record">Record</string>
    <string name="add_place_information">Add Place Information</string>
    <string name="finish_recording">Finish Recording</string>
    <string name="place_name">place name</string>
    <string name="place_address">Place Address</string>
    <string name="longitude_and_latitude">Longitude and Latitude</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_sound2">Add Sound</string>
    <string name="describe_the_sound">describe the sound…</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy">privacy settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_sounds">SearchSoundsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_walks">WalksActivity</string>
    <string name="project_map_of_blois">Project Map of Blois</string>
    <string name="search_by_keyword">Search by Keyword</string>
    <string name="explore_by_geocoding">Explore by Geocoding</string>
    <string name="explore_by_people">Explore by People</string>
    <string name="explore_walking_tous">Explore Walking Tous</string>
    <string name="privacy_setting">Privacy Setting</string>
    <string name="share_your_sound">Share your sound</string>
    <string name="this_primary_user">This sound was recorded by</string>
    <string name="play_sound">play</string>
    <string name="detail_map_of_blois">detail : map of Blois</string>
    <string name="see_more_about_this_user">See more about this user</string>
    <string name="this_sound_was_recorded_by">This sound was recorded by</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="user_details">User details</string>
    <string name="record_button">record button</string>
    <string name="application_tour">Application Tour</string>
    <string name="click_for_more_details_about_sound">click for more details about sound</string>
    <string name="setting_and_privacy">Setting and Privacy</string>
    <string name="LongLat">LongLat</string>
    <string name="more_about_this_user">more about this user</string>
    <string name="get_new_place_from_map">Get New Place From Map</string>
    <string name="place_id">Place ID</string>
    <string name="connect_this_place_to_a_sound">Connect this place to a sound</string>
    <string name="attribution">Attribution</string>
    <string name="powered_by_google">powered by google</string>
    <string name="images_of_project">images of project</string>
    <string name="user">user</string>
    <string name="people_using_the_application">people using the application</string>
    <string name="mobile_application_terms_and_conditions">Mobile Application Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="i_have_read_and_understand_the_condition_of_use">I have read and understand the condition of use</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph2">By installing the Application on your terminal and / or by accessing the Application, as a visitor and / or user, you accept unconditionally and without reservation the entire UGS defined hereafter. If you do not wish to accept these Terms, we request that you do not access the Application. Any visit and / or use of the Application must be done in compliance with these GTC.</string>
    <string name="subhead1">Article 1. DEFINITIONS</string>
    <string name="paragraph3">Terms beginning with a capital letter within these Terms, whether used singly or in the plural, shall have the meanings given to them below:</string>
    <string name="please_read_text">Please Read Text</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="please_read_the_condtions_of_use_agreement">I do not agree or have not read the terms of use</string>
    <string name="i_have_read_and_understand_condtions_of_use_agreement">I have read and understand Conditions of Use Agreement</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph4">\"Application\" means the software application \"Blois: Listening\" published and provided by the Artist, providing access to the Services, which is available free of charge from Apple\'s \"Apple Store\" and Google\'s \"Google Play Store\" to be downloaded by the User on his terminal Apple iOS and Android. The Application also includes Content, software, programs, tools (programming, navigation, …), databases, operating systems, documentation and all other elements and services of which it is composed, updates and new versions that can be made to the Application by the Artist.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead2">Article 2. PURPOSE OF THE APPLICATION</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph5">\"Content\" means, without limitation, the structure of the Application, editorial content, drawings, illustrations, images, photographs, graphic charts, trademarks, logos, acronyms , audiovisual works, multimedia works, visual content, audio and sound content, and any other content within the Application and / or any other component of the Application.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph6">\"Services\" refers to the various features and services offered by the Application.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph7">\"Site\" means the official website of the Blois: Learn to Listen whose address is the following: www.savoir-ecouter.aprille.net</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph8">\"Site\" means the official website of the Blois: Learn to Listen whose address is the following: www.savoir-ecouter.aprille.net</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph9">\"User\" or \"You\" means a natural or legal person who has previously obtained the authorization of his parents or the person having parental authority and who has downloaded the Application for his own needs, strictly personal and non-commercial, non-profit, direct or indirect.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph1">The present general conditions of use (hereinafter referred to as \"GCU\") are intended to determine the rules for the use of the mobile application \"Blois: Knowledge Listen\" (hereinafter referred to as the \"Application\") published by the \'Artist, Aprille Best Glover (hereinafter referred to as the \"Artist\").</string>
    <string name="privacylast">privacyLast</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead3">Article 3. ACCESS TO THE APPLICATION</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph10">The purpose of the Application is to give you access to information and news about the City of Blois proposed by the Artist and to allow you to make a reservation of services through a hyperlink leading you to the page of reservation of the Site.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph11">Several Services may be offered to the User and in particular:</string>
    <string name="privacylist1a">- the plan of the Blois: Learn to Listen / itineraries;</string>
    <string name="privacylist1b">- Geolocation;</string>
    <string name="privacylist1c">- les fonctionnalités de partage avec les réseaux sociaux de Facebook et Twitter ;</string>
    <string name="privacylist1d">- Practical information;</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph12">This list is not exhaustive and can be modified at any time by Blois: Knowing Listen without its responsibility being able to be engaged as such by anybody.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead4">Article 4. GEOLOCATION</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph3">Terms beginning with a capital letter within these Terms, whether used singly or in the plural, shall have the meanings given to them below:</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead1">Article 1. DEFINITIONS</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph13">To access and use the Application, you must have a compatible phone or a mobile terminal and access to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph14">The application can be downloaded free of charge from the \"Apple Store\" and \"Google Play Store\" platforms on the following mobile devices:</string>
    <string name="privacylist2b">- mobile phone with Android® OS 4.4 operating system up to OS 4.4.</string>
    <string name="privacylist2a">- Apple® iphone® mobile phone with the iOS operating system on iOS 8 or iOS 9</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph15">The software version of the Application may be updated from time to time to add new features and services.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph16">The use of the geolocation functionality of the Application requires the prior express consent of the user to be geolocated. To do this, the user will have to activate the geolocation function directly in the settings of his mobile terminal if he wishes and accept that the Application can use it. This feature can be deactivated or activated at any time and without charge.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph17">Thanks to the acceptance of the GPS-based geolocation function of the mobile phone and the Application, the user can:</string>
    <string name="privacylist3a">- be guided during the calculation of itineraries in the City of Blois;</string>
    <string name="privacylist3b">- participate in the artistic project;</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph18">The Application is offered free of charge to Users without subscription costs from the mobile operator, excluding connection costs and access to the Internet network and any additional cost invoiced for loading the data.</string>
    <string name="privacylist3c">- receive messages of an informative nature during the session of use of the Application.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead5">Article 5. FINANCIAL CONDITIONS</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead6">Article 6. APPLICATION OF CGU</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph19">The TOUs are applicable to any User of the Application and the Services.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph20">The User is invited to read carefully and at each visit the CGU which are accessible by hyperlink on the home page of the Application and can be modified at any time and without notice by the Artist.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead7">Article 7. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OF THE APPLICATION</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph22">The Artist is the exclusive owner of all the intellectual property rights relating to the Application and its Content, subject to the rights of which Blois: Learn to Listen operates the license and is available on www.savoir-ecouter.aprille.net/legal-conditions-of-use/</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph21">The Application may be updated on a regular basis. In this respect, any Application downloaded by a User is valid for a limited period of time, taking into account the updates to be downloaded imperatively and any technical, legislative or regulatory developments that the Artist does not control.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead8">Article 8. LICENSE OF USE</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph24">The Artist grants the User a personal right to use the Application, Content and Services, which is non-exclusive, revocable, non-transferable, non-transferable, worldwide and free of charge solely for his own purposes, use of the Application and the Services, to the exclusion of any other purpose.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph25">It is strictly forbidden for the User to access and / or use the source codes of the Application and / or software components of the Application.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph26">The User does not acquire any intellectual property rights over the Application, the Content and / or the Services or any rights other than those conferred herein.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph27">This license does not confer any right of use to the User on the Content. The User is therefore prohibited from reproducing, representing, adapting and / or exploiting either Content.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph28">The User expressly undertakes that the use of the Application does not in any way infringe the rights of the Artist, and in particular that such use does not constitute an act of infringement, unfair or parasitic competition content.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph23">Without prejudice to the provisions of article 7, none of the provisions of the GCU may be interpreted as an assignment, transfer, sale, concession, license, loan, lease, operating license granted directly or indirectly by the Artist for the benefit of the User on the Application its Content and / or the Services.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead9">Article 9. OBLIGATIONS OF THE USER</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph29">The User expressly undertakes:</string>
    <string name="privacylist4a">- to download the Application on its equipment exclusively for personal and non-commercial use;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4b">- not to reproduce permanently or temporarily the Application, in whole or in part, by any means and in any form;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4c">- not to use software or processes intended to copy the Content without the prior written permission of the Artist.</string>
    <string name="privacylist4d">- not to adapt, modify, translate, transcribe, arrange, compile, decompile, assemble, disassemble, transcode, or reverse engineer all or part of the Application, Services and / or Content;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4e">- not to export the Application, to merge all or part of the Application with other computer programs;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4f">- to make short citations, analyzes and reproductions intended for press reviews and other uses expressly authorized by law within the limits and conditions laid down by the latter and subject, in particular, to mention the names of the authors and the editorial source;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4g">- to expressly waive the use of software or devices likely to disrupt the proper functioning of the Application or to take action likely to impose a disproportionate burden on the Blois infrastructure:</string>
    <string name="privacylist4h">- not to extract or re-use, including for private purposes, without the prior written permission of the Artist, a substantial part of the contents of the databases and archives constituted by the Application;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4i">- not to put in place systems likely to hijack the Application and / or the Content in whole or in part, or likely to violate these GCU;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4j">- to inform the Artist as soon as he is aware of an act of piracy and in particular of any unlawful or non-contractual use of the Application and / or the Content whatever the mode of distribution;</string>
    <string name="privacylist4k">- not to sell, rent, sublicense or distribute the Application and / or the Content in any way to third parties.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead10">Article 10. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL DATA</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph30">Any personal data that may be collected in connection with the use of the Application will be processed and kept in accordance with the law n ° 78-017 of January 6, 1978 relating to the Computing, Files and Liberties modified.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph31">The refusal to provide certain personal data may deprive you of access to certain Services.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph32">In the event of the disclosure of personal data, You have the right to access, rectify and object data which You may exercise on request at the following address: Aprille Best Glover - 22 La Grand \'Rue - 41800 Lavardin - France.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph34">Access and use of the Application is at the User\'s own risk. The Application and the software are provided \"as is\" and \"as available\" without warranty of any kind.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph35">It is the responsibility of any User to take all appropriate measures to protect his / her own data and / or software stored on his / her computer and telephone equipment against any attack.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph36">The User declares to know and accept the characteristics and limitations of the Internet network and, in particular, the functional characteristics and technical performance of the Internet; problems related to connection and / or access to the Internet and / or websites; problems related to network availability and congestion; problems related to network failure or saturation; problems with transit time, access to posted information, response times for displaying, viewing, querying, or otherwise transferring data; the risk of interruption; the lack of protection of certain data against possible misappropriation or piracy; the risks of contamination by possible viruses circulating on the said networks, etc. for which the responsibility of Blois: Learn to Listen can not be engaged. the Artist can not be held responsible:</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead12">Article 12. LIMITATION OF WARRANTY</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead11">Article 11. AVAILABILITY OF THE APPLICATION</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph33">Blois: Learn to Listen is committed to making its best efforts to secure access, consultation and use of the Application Services. The Application is accessible 24 hours a day, 7 days a week except in the case of force majeure or the occurrence of an event outside the control of the Artist and subject to possible breakdowns and maintenance operations necessary for the proper functioning of the \'Application. Maintenance may be carried out without prior notice to Users.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph37">The Artist can not be held responsible:</string>
    <string name="privacylist5a">- in case of default, loss, delay or error of transmission of data which are beyond its control;</string>
    <string name="privacylist5b">- the sending of messages and / or data and to a false, erroneous or incomplete address;</string>
    <string name="privacylist5c">- if data were not received for any reason whatsoever, or if the data it received was illegible or impossible to process;</string>
    <string name="privacylist5d">- in the event that the User is unable to access or use the Site, the Application and / or the Services for any reason whatsoever;</string>
    <string name="privacylist5e">- if, for any reason, the connection was to be interrupted.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph38">Furthermore, the artist declines all responsibility in case of misuse of the terminal and / or incident related to the use of the terminal when using the Application. the Artist can under no circumstances be held liable for any damages of any kind whatsoever caused to Users, their terminals, their computer and telephone equipment and the data stored therein or the consequences thereof their personal, professional or commercial activity.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead13">Article 13. DEVELOPMENT OF THE GENERAL CONDITIONS OF USE</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph39">The applicable TOSs are those in force at the date of the User\'s connection and use of the Application.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph40">The Artist reserves the right to modify, at any time, all or part of the provisions of the GCU without advance warning or prior information of the Users in order to adapt them to the evolutions of the Services, technical, legal or jurisprudential evolutions or in place of new services.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph41">Any changes made by the Artist to the CGU will be brought to the attention of the Users by their simple placing on line. They are deemed to be accepted without reservation by any User who accesses the Application after the said placing on line. the Artist invites all Users to consult regularly the GCU.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph42">Any new Service incorporating new techniques or new features improving the quality of the existing Services will also be subject to these Terms unless expressly provided otherwise.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead14">Article 14. TERMINATION</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph43">The Artist may terminate the use of the Application at any time by giving you notice of termination.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph44">Upon termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to You will be terminated and You shall cease all use of the Application.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead15">Article 15. CONTACT</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph45">Any questions relating to the Application and / or the Services must be addressed by postal mail to the following address:</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph46">Aprille Best Glover - 22 La Grand - Rue - 41800 Lavardin - France.</string>
    <string name="privacysubhead16">Article 16. APPLICABLE LAW</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph47">These GTC are subject to French law.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph48">Any dispute or dispute relating to the execution or interpretation of this by-law which can not be settled amicably between the parties will be submitted to the competent courts within the jurisdiction of the Court of Appeal of Orléans.</string>
    <string name="privacyparagraph49">Done at Lavardin, on 21 September 2017.</string>
    <string name="Init">Initializing Database… This may take some time.</string>
    <string name="initializing_database_this_may_take_some_time">Initializing Database... This may take some time.</string>
    <string name="sound_user">sounds of User :</string>
    <string name="place_sounds">Place Sounds :</string>
    <string name="logo_of_the_city_of_blois">Logo of the city of Blois</string>
    <string name="thanks_par1">The artist would like to thank the city of Blois, the Caisse des Depots and the association Odeur de la Color for their technical and financial support. In addition, she would like to a special thanks the project\'s institutional partners (ALCV, the APF, the hospital center of Blois, the Espace Mirabeau, the Espace Quinière, FabLab Robert-Houdin, Lycée horticole public de Blois, the Maison des Provinces, the Médiathèque Maurice-Genevoix, the Observatoire Loire, EHPAD La Roselière and Association Valentin Haüy)</string>
    <string name="thanks_par2">Finally, the artist would like to thank the hundreds of residents of Blois who generously gave the time and creativity to make this project a success.</string>
    <string name="thanks_par3">The website is www.blois.odeurdelacouleur.info.  This project is made possible by the support of la Caisse des Dépôts, http://www.caissedesdepots.fr</string>
    <string name="logo_ville">logo of city of Blois</string>
    <string name="logo_of_caisse_des_depots">Logo of Caisse des Depots</string>
    <string name="logo_of_the_association_odeur_de_la_couleur">logo of the association Odeur de la Couleur</string>
    <string name="title_activity_thank_you">Thanks</string>
    <string name="add_sound">Add Sound</string>
    <string name="sound_description">sound description</string>
    <string name="lets_share">Let\'s share</string>
    <string name="add_sounds">add sound</string>
    <string name="Initializing">Initializing</string>
    <string name="logos_of_partner_organization">logos of partner organization</string>
    <string name="exception">exception</string>
    <string name="selected_place_name">Selected Place Name</string>
    <string name="select_mail_application_title">Email to Share</string>
    <string name="edit">edit</string>
    <string name="rec_finished">Recording Completed</string>
    <string name="number_of_places">Number of Places</string>
    <string name="pick_from_google_map">pick_from_google_map</string>
    <string name="connect_this_place_to_sound">connect this place to sound</string>
    <string name="play">play</string>
    <string name="edit_sound_text">Edit Sound Text</string>
    <string name="edit_sound_name">Edit Sound Name</string>
    <string name="edit_sound_desc">Edit sound description</string>
    <string name="edit_sound_descript">Edit Sound Description</string>
    <string name="edit_sound_name2">Edit Sound Name</string>
    <string name="sounds">Sounds :</string>
    <string name="see_your_sound_collection">See your sound collection</string>
    <string name="title_activity_primary_user">Your Sound Collection</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps_walk">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_walk_detail">WalkDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="distance">distance :</string>
    <string name="walk_name">Walk Name</string>
    <string name="walk_description">Walk description</string>
    <string name="title_activity_walk_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="initializing">Intializing DataBase May take some time</string>
    <string name="forward">Forward</string>
    <string name="parcours">Parcours :</string>
    <string name="start">start</string>
    <string name="finish">finish</string>
    <string name="kilometers">kilomètres</string>
    <string name="distance_plus">Distance :</string>
    <string name="stage">Stage</string>

</resources>
